Guide to the Yasser Alwan Collection AD.MC.002
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Series II: Egypt, 1895-1971 (Box 1-7)
  - Munira Hanem Postcard Series
    - A hand-colored postcard of an orange and a purple flower with a lake in the background. 13.7 x 8.7 cm, Undated; cuid1105; Alfred Noyer Studio, Paris (Box 5, Folder 23)
      Postcards; Unknown Locations; Lakes; Outdoors; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; English Writing; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting
    - Postcard of a baby in a cabbage patch. Same baby from ref1135. 13.4 x 8.8 cm, Undated; cuid1106 (Box 5, Folder 23)
      Unknown Locations; Postcards; Children; Arabic Writing; Individual Portraits; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting
    - Postcard of a baby in a cabbage patch. Same baby from ref1134. 13.7 x 8.8 cm, Undated; cuid1107 (Box 5, Folder 23)
      Unknown Locations; Individual Portraits; Postcards; Children; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting
    - A hand-colored postcard of a view of a boat from a window. 14.2 x 9.0 cm, Undated; cuid1108 (Box 5, Folder 23)
      Boats/Ships; Arabic Writing; Postcards; Unknown Locations; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting
    - A hand-colored postcard of a girl in a mint green dress and pink flowers. 13.6 x 8.7 cm, Undated; cuid1116 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      Postcards; Arabic Writing; Unknown Locations; Individual Portraits; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Girls; Photographic Prints; Children; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting
    - Postcard of a blonde woman in a pink head cover (same woman as ref1128). 13.9 x 8.7 cm, Undated; cuid1118 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      Individual Portraits; Unknown Locations; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Head Covers/Veils; Furnishings; Women; Postcards; Photographic Prints
    - A hand-colored postcard of hands holding flowers with a blue ribbon. French text "Souvenir of a sincere friendship". 8.9 x 14.0 cm, Undated; cuid1120 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      Postcards; Arabic Writing; Unknown Locations; French Writing; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Eid
  - Two Armenian women with a basket of flowers (link ref78). 13.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated; cuid64 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Painted Backdrops; Alexandria, Egypt; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Gelatin Silver Prints; Women; Group Portraits; Furnishings; Jewelry
  - Two Armenian women holding a book (link ref77). 13.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated; cuid65 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Alexandria, Egypt; Women; Studio Photography; Furnishings; Painted Backdrops; Books; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Jewelry
  - Two Armenian women with a painted moon backdrop. 13.5 x 8.5 cm, Undated; cuid66 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Women; Painted Backdrops; Cairo, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Furnishings; Carpets/Rugs; Bags/Purses; Clocks/Watches; Jewelry
  - An Armenian family portrait, two girls wear matching dresses and a boy wears a nautical outfit. 13.7 x 8.8 cm, Undated; cuid67 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Men; Women; Children; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Jewelry; Maritime/Nautical Outfits; Painted Backdrops; Alexandria, Egypt; Group Portraits; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Facial Hair
  - An Egyptian man wearing a tarbouche and eye glasses. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, Undated; cuid68 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Photographic Prints; Painted Backdrops; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Egypt; Studio Photography; Fez/Tarboush; Men; Facial Hair; Hats
  - A man wearing a tarbouche and robe, in front of a painted backdrop. 13.2 x 8.3 cm, Undated; cuid69 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Fez/Tarboush; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Painted Backdrops; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Men; Facial Hair; Carpets/Rugs; Furnishings; Hats
  - A young man wearing a tarbouche and long black coat in front of a painted backdrop. 13.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated; cuid70 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Fez/Tarboush; Gelatin Silver Prints; Kafr El-Zayat, Gharbia, Egypt; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Painted Backdrops; Men; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Furnishings
  - Two men wearing tarbouches and suits. 13.5 x 8.5 cm, Undated; cuid71 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Men; Facial Hair; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Fez/Tarboush; Studio Photography; Facial Hair; Hats
  - A man wearing a suit and tarbouche, with a boy seated on a table. 13.6 x 8.6 cm, 28 March 1926; cuid72 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Studio Photography; Fez/Tarboush; Arabic Writing; Signatures; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Children; Boys; Facial Hair; Furnishings; Pens/Inkwells; Hats
  - A man wearing a suit and tarbouche leaning on a pedestal. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, Undated; cuid73 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Studio Photography; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Painted Backdrops; Men; Egypt; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Fez/Tarboush; Facial Hair; Furnishings; Hats
  - A man wearing a suit and tarbouche. 13.7 x 8.7 cm, Undated; cuid74 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Fez/Tarboush; Studio Photography; Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Facial Hair; Hats
  - A man wearing a light pinstriped in a suit and round glasses. 12.3 x 8.8 cm, Undated; cuid75 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Egypt; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
  - A man wearing a long dark robe and cap with a tassel. 13.8 x 8.8 cm, 16 December 1923; cuid76 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Studio Photography; Facial Hair; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Facial Hair; Hats; Individual Portraits; Hats; Regional/National Dress; Signatures
  - A man in a dark three-piece suit and glasses. Photo Varjabedian Zagazio. 13.7 x 8.6 cm, Undated; cuid77 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Zagazig, Egypt; Facial Hair
  - A man wearing a three-piece suit, resting on a tall side table in front of a painted backdrop. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; cuid78 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Individual Portraits; Men; Furnishings; Photographic Prints; Painted Backdrops; Studio Photography; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Facial Hair
  - A studio portrait of a woman and a man posing with three girls and a boy wearing a sailor's outfit. 13.8 x 8.8 cm, Undated; cuid79 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Maritime/Nautical Outfits; Egypt; Men; Women; Children; Girls; Boys; Jewelry; Group Portraits; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Facial Hair; Furnishings
  - A group of ten men, with two children. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; cuid80 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Photographic Prints; Restaurants/bars; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Men; Gatherings; Egypt; Group Portraits; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Facial Hair; Hats; Bow Ties; Drinks/Beverages; Tea/Coffee
  - A portrait of a soldier with the number '51' on his uniform. 13.7 x 8.7 cm, Undated; cuid81 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Military/Soldiers; Painted Backdrops; Men; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia
  - A studio portrait of a man and four women. Armenian writing on the reverse side: In memory of A. Aufian family. (signed by N. Aufian) (linked ref265). 13.8 x 8.4 cm, Undated; cuid82 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Armenian Writing; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Men; Women; Facial Hair; Furnishings; Jewelry
  - An Armenian family, a young man is leaning on some books on a pedestal. 13.7 x 8.7 cm, Undated; cuid83 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Painted Backdrops; Egypt; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jewelry; Furnishings; Photographic Prints; Books; Group Portraits; Men; Women
  - A blonde Egyptian woman wearing long earrings and an off the shoulder top. 11.3 x 7.5 cm, Undated; cuid84 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Arabic writing at the back
    Photographic Prints; Egypt; Jewelry; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Arabic Writing; Women; Individual Portraits
  - A man wearing a tarbouche and a light striped suit. 13.5 x 8.1 cm, Undated; cuid85 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Arabic Writing; Facial Hair; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Men; Individual Portraits; Fez/Tarboush; Cairo, Egypt; Facial Hair; Hats
  - An Egyptian man in a long double-breasted coat, holding a book. 13.6 x 8.5 cm, Undated; cuid86 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Photographic Prints; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Furnishings; Men; Books; Facial Hair; Painted Backdrops
  - An Egyptian official wearing a sash and medals. 13.6 x 8.5 cm, Undated; cuid87 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Officials; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Fez/Tarboush; Photographic Prints; Medals/Insignia; Studio Photography; Men; Individual Portraits; Bow Ties; Facial Hair; Hats
  - A Coptic clergyman kneeling on a carpet, in a religious ceremony. 13.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated; cuid88 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Priests/Clergymen; Religious Ceremony; Men; Photographic Prints; Religious Crosses; Ceremonies; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Religious Crosses; Studio Photography; Facial Hair; Group Portraits
  - A man in formal attire leaning on a column. 13.2 x 8.2 cm, Undated; cuid89 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Studio Photography; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Individual Portraits; Men; Furnishings; Egypt; Photographic Prints; Painted Backdrops; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A woman holding a girl sitting on a cushion. 13.6 x 8.2 cm, Undated; cuid90 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Studio Photography; Girls; Women; Children; Photographic Prints; Cairo, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Furnishings
  - A man wearing military uniform and two boys wearing suits. 13.7 x 8.5 cm, 26 September 1942; cuid91 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    writing at the back
    Military/Soldiers; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Men; Boys; Tanta/Tantah, Egypt; Uniforms; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Children; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Furnishings
  - A group of Egyptian men in front of Pompey's Pillar, Alexandria, Egypt. 13.6 x 8.8 cm, Undated; cuid92 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Photographic Prints; Fez/Tarboush; Alexandria, Egypt; Men; Group Portraits; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Facial Hair; Hats
  - A group of young men in tarbouches, posing with a football (linked ref 113). 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; cuid93 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Fez/Tarboush; Football; Sports; Men; Group Portraits; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Facial Hair; Bow Ties; Hats
  - A group of young men in tarbouches, posing with a football. (linked ref112). 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; cuid94 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Fez/Tarboush; Football; Men; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Sports; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Facial Hair; Hats
  - An Egyptian woman wearing a shoulderless dress. 13.8 x 8.5 cm, Undated; cuid95 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Studio Photography; Women; Individual Portraits
  - A woman posing in front of a mirror. 13.5 x 8.6 cm, Undated; cuid96 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Women; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Jewelry; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt
  - A girl wearing a cross. Text on reverse: "Souvenir a la petite Therese". 13.5 x 8.8 cm, 26 May 1934; cuid97; S. Zoulis, Cairo (Egypt) (Box 1, Folder 11)
    French writing at the back
    Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Girls; French Writing; Photographic Prints; Cairo, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Religious Crosses; Jewelry; Religious Crosses; Furnishings
  - An Egyptian man in a light suit and mustache. 11.8 x 8.1 cm, Undated; cuid98 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Men; Individual Portraits; Facial Hair; Facial Hair; Gelatin Silver Prints; Tunis, Tunisia; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
  - An Egyptian man wearing a three-piece suit, with a small pin. 13.4 x 8.5 cm, Undated; cuid99 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Arabic Writing; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Photographic Prints; Facial Hair
  - A man wearing a waistcoat holding a shisha in hand, a child sits nearby. 13.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated; cuid100 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Signatures; Photographic Prints; Shops; Shisha/Hookah/Nargiles; Smoking; Men; Children; Egypt; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Shisha/Hookah/Nargiles; Girls; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
  - Three men posing in front of a painted backdrop, one holds a cane. 13.8 x 8.7 cm, 3 November 1925; cuid101 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Canes/Walking Sticks; English Writing; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Painted Backdrops; Men; Egypt; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Fez/Tarboush; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Facial Hair; Carpets/Rugs; Hats
  - Two men resting on a column, one holds a flywhisk. 13.6 x 8.5 cm, Undated; cuid102 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Furnishings; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Fez/Tarboush; Painted Backdrops; Cairo, Egypt; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Facial Hair; Hats
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a pin-stripe suit. 13.8 x 8.5 cm, Undated; cuid103 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Men; Fez/Tarboush; Tanta/Tantah, Egypt; Tanta/Tantah, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Hats
  - A studio portrait of a man and a woman wearing a floral patterned dress and earrings (linked ref228). 13.7 x 8.6 cm, 15 October 1928; cuid104 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Fez/Tarboush; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Bow Ties; Jewelry; Women; Men; Signatures; Group Portraits; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Facial Hair
  - A woman and man standing in front of a painted backdrop, the woman wears a dark dress, and the man a double-breasted suit. 13.8 x 9.0 cm, 11 April 1971; cuid105 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Painted Backdrops; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Clocks/Watches; Women; Men; Group Portraits; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Furnishings; Facial Hair; Carpets/Rugs; Prayer Beads
  - A woman sitting on a sofa with a man standing next to her, in front of a painted backdrop. 13.4 x 8.8 cm, Undated; cuid106 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Women; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Furnishings; Painted Backdrops; Alexandria, Egypt; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Group Portraits
  - A woman seated, with two men standing beside her in front of a painted backdrop. 13.8 x 8.7 cm, Undated; cuid107 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Photographic Prints; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Women; Men; Studio Photography; Group Portraits; Alexandria, Egypt; Painted Backdrops; Facial Hair; Jewelry
  - An Armenian man in uniform, sitting in front of a painted backdrop. 13.8 x 8.9 cm, Undated; cuid108 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Studio Photography; Armenian Writing; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Painted Backdrops; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Facial Hair; Furnishings
  - Three women wearing dark clothing, posing in front of a painted backdrop. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; cuid109 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jewelry; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Egypt; Women
  - A Christian family, the child holds a cane and wears a cross. 13.7 x 8.7 cm, Undated; cuid110 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Alexandria, Egypt; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Religious Crosses; Religious Crosses; Boys; Painted Backdrops; Women; Photographic Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Furnishings; Religious Crosses; Jewelry
  - A portrait of a man and a woman sitting on a stool, the woman wears. Text on reverse: To my beloved sister Mrs. Mariam Asufian on the oassion of New Year and Christmas. (Signed: Malvina Hekimian). 13.6 x 8.7 cm, 31 December 1932; cuid111 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Armenian Writing; Nikaia, Attica, Greece; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Furnishings; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Painted Backdrops; Men; Photographic Prints; Women; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
  - A girl in a white dress on a rooftop with a young woman standing behind her. 13.8 x 8.8 cm, Undated; cuid112 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Children; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Egypt; Group Portraits
  - A man wearing a tarbouche and a light colored suit standing in a corner. 13.6 x 8.6 cm, 10 May 1932; cuid113 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Men; Facial Hair; Individual Portraits; Fez/Tarboush; Arabic Writing; Signatures; Tiles; Photographic Prints; Facial Hair; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats
  - A man wearing a tarbouche and a bow tie, with his hand in his pocket. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, Undated; cuid114 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Bow Ties; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Kafr El-Zayat, Gharbia, Egypt; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Men; Egypt; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Fez/Tarboush; Facial Hair; Hats
  - A young man wearing a tarbouche and a suit with a patterned tie. 13.6 x 8.8 cm, Undated; cuid115 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Tanta/Tantah, Egypt; Boys; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Tanta/Tantah, Egypt; Fez/Tarboush; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Children; Hats
  - A man wearing a tarbouche with a flywhisk in his hand, sitting on a table. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, Undated; cuid116 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Alexandria, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Painted Backdrops; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Men; Fez/Tarboush; Gelatin Silver Prints; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Facial Hair; Furnishings; Hats
  - A man wearing round glasses and a bow tie. 13.6 x 8.5 cm, 18 February 1933; cuid117 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Tanta/Tantah, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Fez/Tarboush; Bow Ties; Men; Tanta/Tantah, Egypt; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Signatures; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Facial Hair; Pens/Inkwells; Hats
  - A man with a mustache wearing circular dark glasses.13.8 x 8.5 cm, Undated; cuid118 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Cairo, Egypt; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Photographic Prints; Men; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
  - A man wearing a suit with a striped tie, standing with his hands behind his back. 13.7 x 8.7 cm, Undated; cuid119 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Studio Photography; Fez/Tarboush; Gelatin Silver Prints; Cairo, Egypt; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Hats
  - A man wearing a white gown and holding prayer beads and a flywhisk, sitting in a garden. Arabic text on reverse: Zahle, Jebel Lubnan, Lebanon. 13.6 x 8.4 cm, 6 August 1946; cuid120 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Facial Hair; Men; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Gardens; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Arabic Writing; Prayer Beads; Lebanon; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Zahle, Beqaa, Lebanon; Hats; Signatures; Canes/Walking Sticks
  - A group of boys at school, one sits at a typewriter. 8.9 x 14.0 cm, Undated; cuid121 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Group Portraits; Hats; Typewriters; Fez/Tarboush; Photographic Prints; Teachers; Qena, Egypt; Men; Schools/Education; Boys; Arabic Writing; Students; Machines; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Typewriters; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Regional/National Dress
  - A man in a dark suit with a short mustache. 13.6 x 9.1 cm, Undated; cuid122 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Facial Hair; Individual Portraits; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Facial Hair; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Individual Portraits
  - A group of men wearing suits and tarbouches at a ceremony. 8.4 x 13.9 cm, Undated; cuid123 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Fez/Tarboush; Canes/Walking Sticks; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Men; Group Portraits; Audiences/Spectators; Photographic Prints; Events/Occasions; Ceremonies; Girls; Children; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Facial Hair; Hats
  - A group pose in a home setting. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, Undated; cuid124 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Photographic Prints; Houses; Women; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Furnishings; Egypt; Group Portraits
  - A man wearing a dark three-piece suit and patterned tie. 13.5 x 8.7 cm, Undated; cuid125 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Individual Portraits; Egypt; Painted Backdrops; Arabic Writing; Signatures; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Men; Facial Hair; Photographic Prints
  - A group of boy scouts and their teachers. 8.9 x 14.0 cm, Undated; cuid126 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Uniforms; Arabic Writing; Children; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Scouts; Schools/Education; Fez/Tarboush; Buildings; Boys; Qena, Egypt; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Facial Hair; Men; Hats
  - A portrait of a woman seated in a high back chair with a man resting on its arm. 14.0 x 8.9 cm, Undated; cuid127 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Egypt; Studio Photography; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Jewelry; Furnishings; Women; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
  - An oval cropped portrait of a woman wearing a black dress, against a painted backdrop. 13.4 x 8.1 cm, Undated; cuid128 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Painted Backdrops; Egypt; Women; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A man wearing a black suit, resting on a table and standing in front of a curtain. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, 1921; cuid129 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Furnishings; Men; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Egypt; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
  - A boy wearing a tarbouche, leaning on the back of a chair. 13.6 x 8.5 cm, Undated; cuid130 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Fez/Tarboush; Egypt; Furnishings; Individual Portraits; Boys; Painted Backdrops; Children; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Hats
  - An oval cropped portrait of a man seated in a chair wearing a light suit with a bow tie. 14.1 x 8.7 cm, Undated; cuid131 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Facial Hair; Men; Individual Portraits; Furnishings; Facial Hair; Photographic Prints; Bow Ties
  - An Armenian man wearing a dark suit and patterned tie. 13.6 x 8.8 cm, 21 May 1928; cuid132 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Armenian Writing; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Facial Hair; Alexandria, Egypt; Men; Individual Portraits; Facial Hair; Signatures
  - A wood supply warehouse (depot de bois) entrance. Egyptian postal stamp on reverse. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, 2 October 1958; cuid133 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Architecture; Postal Stamps; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Construction; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; French Writing; Cairo, Egypt; Men; Group Portraits; Streets/Roads; Signatures
  - A man in a white shirt and a young woman wearing a checked dress, surrounded by flowers (linked ref161). 13.6 x 8.9 cm, 6 December 1970; cuid134 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Egypt; Women; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Studio Photography; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Furnishings; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Group Portraits